"As you wish."
(Howard:)You know, Sheldon,
none of this would've happened
(Howard:)if I hadn't tried to help you.
(Sheldon:)It also wouldn't have happened
if, in the early universe,
(Sheldon:)hydrogen was a little more common
or a little less common.
(Sheldon:)This is fun. Your turn.
(Amy:)-Gentlemen.
-Hey, Amy.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Leonard:)That was kind of icy.
You two okay?
(Sheldon:)We're fine.
As Howard advised,
(Sheldon:)she's merely respecting
our professional boundaries.
(Leonard:)Smart. Take relationship advice
from a man
(Leonard:)who spent last night
braiding Raj's hair.
(Sheldon:)You make a good point.
(Sheldon:)It would appear I was worried
for nothing.
(Sheldon:)Look at her, desperately wishing
she was over here at the cool table.
(Sheldon:)Don't worry, little moth.
The flame will come to you.